[Rogue] Previously on X-Men...
Just hard to believe that we might
finally be able to punch our ticket home.
- [fire crackling]
- What is awaiting you there?
[Rogue] It's more about
what's not waiting for me.
Someone... I lost.
Someone... special.
[En Sabah Nur] Everyone
I have ever known. I've lost.
Love is pain.
[Rogue] And the only thing
that makes life worth living...
[chuckles softly] And there's the rub.
I do hope you get to
experience it one day.
For all our sakes.
[♪ theme music playing]
[screaming]
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
How? How could this be?
[fireworks exploding]
[♪ enchanting music playing]
[inhales. exhales]
[sighs]
Remember. chère...
- [♪ music ends abruptly]
- Oh.
...some things be deeper than skin.
[gasps]
[screaming in pain]
[screaming. panting]
Hold on. Jean.
I thought we said no powers.
It's not my fault
that your tells are so obvious.
Your turn. Professor. Are you in or out?
[sighs] Sadly. [chuckles] I must fold.
Well. that leaves myself
und the very quiet Dr. McCoy.
Don't let him sucker you in. Beast.
Aces over eights.
The Dead Man's Hand.
Fortunately. mine is much livelier.
Three threes
from your fellow friend in blue.
- [gasps]
- [Jean chuckles] Way to go. Beast.
[Nightcrawler] At least tell me
how you broke my streak.
"Life is not always
a matter of holding good cards.
but sometimes playing a poor hand well."
- Jack London.
- [Cyclops] Yeah. yeah.
- Save it for the book club.
- [all laughing]
- [sighs]
- Is everything all right. my child?
Just glad to be among friends.
[alarm blaring]
Now. who pulled the fire alarm?
An unidentified military bomber.
heavily armed with psionic jammers.
Unidentified aircraft.
you are trespassing private airspace.
Please state your purpose.
[Beast] Surely only a madman
would try and breach our EMP field.
[Professor X] This is your final warning.
Alter course immediately.
Hank. prepare to engage.
Wait! I can sense a mind
through the jammers.
Presence drawn to...
me and Scott?
Nathan?
Oh. dear.
- Hi guys. we need help.
- We're coming in for a landing.
[♪ dramatic music playing]
- Son.
- [Jean] Nathan.
It's. um... good to see you again.
Yeah. there's a lot to catch up on.
Right now. there's been a murder.
And that's not even the bad news.
Rogue...
- There's something you need to see.
- [sighs]
[Psylocke] Apocalypse overestimated
his ability to control
a Horseman who's been
resurrected from the grave.
So. what you're saying is.
whatever has been brought back
might not really be Remy?
We'll know when we find him.
Which is why we need you
to use Cerebro to do so.
No way we're helping you
add Gambit to your posse's dirty hitlist!
This isn't about killing him.
It's about undoing the evil in him.
Rogue. years ago. you freed me
from Apocalypse's corruption.
[Psylocke] We sneak you in close
so you can use your gifts
to restore Gambit's soul.
But how do we know
his soul is there to restore?
We have to believe
that a part of Gambit endures.
Such questions will have to wait
until we've recovered him.
That mean we have a deal. Chuck?
On one condition.
this is our rescue mission.
Brute tactics will not be tolerated.
Gambit's not himself.
We're just here to make sure
he doesn't put anyone else in danger.
[Rogue] Gambit's alive?
And he's killed Apocalypse?
We have witnessed our share or miracles.
Huh.
My daddy used to say. a miracle is just
wrapping paper for the next tragedy.
Rogue. this is not the time
for your colorful lamentations.
Remy is back.
I know. Kurt. I know.
And I'm afraid of what that means.
Everything will be fine. sister.
I promise.
We've made some updates. We call it...
Cerebra.
[Professor X] If Gambit is out there.
this will help me find him.
[♪ captivating music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
Mighty untoward.
peekin' at another man's cards.
[gasps. groans]
[Professor X panting]
Professor. did you find him?
[Professor X] I fear there's
more to this darkness
than we have yet to understand.
Just tell us where he's gone.
He's gone home.
Evenin'. Robert. What's goin' on?
[Robert] You tell me. Bella Donna.
It's you who invited us here. no?
Don't be stupid.
Why would I send myself this invitation?
[Gambit] The invitations were mine.
- [♪ dramatic music playing]
- [all gasping]
Surprised to see me?
I know I am.
Remy? But you...
Aw. petite. you don't look so happy
to see your thieving ex.
What the hell happened to you?
What happened. big brother?
- For starters. I died.
- [gasps]
Then the Devil snatched me
out of the grave.
A real bad customer.
[all gasping]
Remy. please.
[Gambit] Don't be scared. chérie.
Death is evolution.
[all groaning]
[all screaming]
[Jubilee] Hey. I...
I'm sorry. I know this will be hard.
Facing Gambit.
Got nothing to be sorry for. sugar.
Remy's weighing on all our hearts.
Can't let regret make it feel heavier.
Heck. probably best
X-Force stayed clear of Remy. anyhow.
Sure. they can be a little intense.
But tracking Apocalypse
these past few months.
I've learned that
you can't shut your heart off.
'Cause that's the thing
that's gonna get you through this.
Family reunion time already?
We wanted to check in...
See how you're holding up.
It must have been strange.
finding Apocalypse.
Not exactly how I'd pictured my destiny.
Why didn't you tell us. Nathan?
That you'd met us as a boy?
Why not reach out when we got back?
Time would have ripped us apart again.
like it always does.
Well. I've about had my fill
of what happened yesterday.
or could tomorrow.
For once. son.
can we focus on what we could be today?
[Jean] A family.
We scout for Gambit quick and quiet.
unless we want X-Factor
and their Mech-Sentinels on our butts.
No way Val Cooper
and her government stooges found us.
I sense no Mech-Sentinel pilots outside.
but I do sense--
A swarm of black holes
where minds and souls should be.
- [missile whistles]
- [explosion]
[all grunting]
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[Bella Donna grunting]
Bella Donna? Robert?
What's he done to ya?
Skip the shock and awe.
Find Gambit. Now!
[all grunting]
- [gasps]
- [groans]
[grunting]
[gasps]
[Rogue grunts]
Remy?
Remy. it's me. It's Rogue.
Apocalypse poisoned your mind.
I can help you.
Just trust me.
[Gambit] You know...
life does flash before our eyes
when we die.
[♪ melancholy music playing]
And when I died...
all I saw...
was you.
[gasps]
What's wrong?
That ain't possible.
Warned you. chère.
Some things. they be deeper than skin.
Sleep.
[gasps]
[Jean] X-Men.
I've lost contact with Rogue.
[both grunting]
I'm on it!
Put her down. Remy. You are not yourself.
[grunts]
[groaning]
Now. neither are you. mon ami.
- [♪ dramatic music playing]
- [tires screeching]
[explosions]
[all grunting]
The wings are coming off.
We gotta go after Gambit.
No. we need every telekinetic
landing this plane
- or we're all toast.
- [straining]
[straining]
We can do this. son. together.
[both grunting]
[screaming]
- [panting]
- [groaning]
[screaming]
[reporter] The Pentagon has confirmed
the plane belonged to X-Force.
They've yet to say if this was
a failed terrorist attack or a crash.
News was spooking the kids.
so I put on The Exorcist.
Didn't get these back
just to play gym coach
while Jean and the others
are blown out of the sky.
The school will be safe with Colossus.
Right now. our family needs us.
And X-Men fight for their own.
Let's move.
[gasps]
Kurt. what's he done to you?
Time to rise. sister. Dinner is served.
And you are the guest of honor.
[♪ slow music playing]
Evenin'. chère.
[chuckles] Siccing your brainwashed
ex on me
is a mighty bold way
to ask a lady out to dinner.
You did always like my unorthodox flair.
Gambit never woulda dreamed
you'd be working with the merc
hunting me down. neither.
Cable? No. Remy.
We were tryin' to save you.
[sighs]
I thought I could.
World's been conspiring
to keep us apart for so long. chère.
We both learned to expect the worst.
But now. now we've been dealt
a whole new hand.
That gap between the man I was
and the one you want
is finally gone.
Or at least. it can be.
This is just so strange.
Getting you back. why.
is all I ever dreamed of.
But now. you're here and...
I don't know if I should be relieved...
or scared.
I ain't crawled outta my grave
to repeat regrets.
This is our second chance.
So. no more holding
my cards close to my chest.
So. here they are. belle.
I learned Apocalypse
ain't no different than us.
He had a love that broke his heart too.
A priestess of ancient Egypt courted him.
convinced him to give her
a piece of his power...
[exclaiming in pain]
[Gambit] Only to betray him.
A trap she laid to seek revenge
for what he did to her people.
[groans]
She done run away with it.
right here to the bayou.
Locals know her as the X-Ternal.
Her relic will make you immortal like me.
It'll bind us together forever.
husband and wife.
And then nothin'. not even death
ever keep us apart again.
[sighs wearily]
How do I know I can trust you?
'Cause I'm offering us a second chance.
You gotta believe in me.
Believe in us. chère.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[distant whoosh]
[♪ suspenseful music continues]
- [squelching]
- [gasps]
The Assassins Guild calls upon
its covenant with the X-Ternal.
Let this tribute awake you from your sleep
and summon you forth...
[rumbling]
- [thunderclap]
- [gasps]
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[thunderclap]
Who dares disturb my slumber?
- C'est moi.
- [External] Remy LeBeau.
This is unexpected.
You have become stained and defiled.
What is it that you seek?
[laughs maniacally]
This is forged
from the very fires of creation.
given to me by Apocalypse.
'Fraid not. it belongs to me.
You stole it from my predecessor.
You dare to defy me?
I have stood by the Devil's side
and glimpsed his dark intents.
I will not indulge a scoundrel
to entertain his--
- [squelching]
- [gasps. groans]
Sorry. gotta cut this game short.
What goes around. come around.
Remy. no!
[sighs] What did you do?
[Gambit] Going all in. chère.
You ready?
Gambit. we don't want to fight you.
But we will.
Stand down. Now.
Remy. please.
If that your bet. mes amis. I call.
[all yelling]
Tides. rise and help cleanse
this foul ritual.
[all gasping. coughing]
[grunting]
[yelling. groaning]
[all groaning]
[Jubilee screaming]
[all screaming]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[groaning. screaming in pain]
[Professor X] Remy.
it's time to end this madness.
[grunts]
[groans]
[Professor X]
In the battlefield of the mind.
my will shall prevail.
Now this be an unexpected delight.
[groans. screams]
Where was this will back in Genosha
when Gambit needed it?
As Jean once used the power of the Phoenix
to bind the M'kraan Crystal.
I now bind you with the power of--
[Professor X groans]
[grunting]
[both grunting]
[Professor X exclaiming in pain]
- [grunts]
- [gasps]
- Remy!
If you can hear me.
- come back to me!
- [exclaiming in pain]
[Gambit] Professor.
Help me. please!
[grunting]
Everyone. close your eyes!
X-Force. Gambit's exposed.
It's time to make our move.
Nathan. no!
- [all gasping]
- We don't want to hurt you.
but be certain that we will.
Cable. what gives?
Sorry. kiddo. Had to play nice
to get close enough for the kill.
Nathan. do not make me
take over your mind.
Apocalypse is in there.
and it's my destiny to kill him.
[gasps]
After all this time.
the teacher has still learned nothing.
You... You're alive.
In here? How?
I would have thought.
after your beloved Magnus.
you might have finally understood.
I always survive!
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[groans]
[groans] Professor!
- [Professor X exclaiming in pain]
- [groans]
[yelling]
Remy!
[♪ dramatic music continues]
Come on. sugar!
[groaning. panting]
[gasps]
[yelling]
[groans. gasps]
[Professor X] X-Men. we must retreat. now!
Kurt. you're back with us?
[grunts]
[machine beeping]
[Professor X] His vitals are faint.
but his neural activity... most strange.
Apocalypse will not stay contained
inside Remy's consciousness much longer.
If we do not move quickly.
he will take him over for good.
[Rogue] I've got you. sugar.
I won't lose you.
Not again.
[Warren] Your honeypot didn't work.
[growls softly]
Enough. Warren.
- It's time to regroup.
- With whom?
It's just us three now.
- [explosion]
- [all gasp]
[Nathan chuckles] If you think
you're taking us in.
you're in for a surprise. pal.
Hey. chief.
You're not the ones we're after.
What do you say to both of us
getting what we want?
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today